grammarflip.com 2016-01-26

# Privacy Policy - GrammarFlip

Remember that your use of GrammarFlip’s services is at all times subject to the Terms of Service which incorporates this Privacy Policy. Any terms we use in this Policy without defining them have the definitions given to them in the Terms of Service.  If you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please send a detailed message to [info@GrammarFlip.com](mailto:info@GrammarFlip.com) and we will try to resolve your concerns.

By using or accessing the Services in any manner, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy, and you hereby consent that we will collect, use, and share your information only in the following ways:

We gather various types of Personal Information from our users, and we use this Personal Information internally in connection with our Services to allow you to set up a user account and profile, to contact you, and to understand how you use the Services.

**GrammarFlip does NOT rent or sell (including for purposes of marketing or advertising) your Personal Information in personally identifiable form to anyone.**

GrammarFlip uses _**aggregate, de-identified user data**_ to enable us to understand how users use parts of the Services, so that we can customize and improve those Services. As part of our use of such information, we may provide such information to our partners (only in a de-identified format) about how our users use our site. We may share this type of **_statistical data_** so that our partners also understand how often people use our Services so as to help provide you with an optimal online experience.

If you are not of legal age (18 years of age) to form a binding contract, you may only use the Services and disclose information to us with your parent’s or legal guardian’s express consent. Review this Privacy Policy with your parent or legal guardian to make sure you understand it.

We only collect Personal Information through the Services from a child under 13 where that student’s school, district, and/or teacher has agreed (via the terms described in the Terms of Service) to obtain parental consent for that child to use the Services and disclose Personal Information to us. A parent or guardian may sign up his or her child for the Services and provide Personal Information about that child to us. However, no child under 13 may send us any Personal Information unless he or she has signed up through his or her school, district or teacher and such school, district or teacher has obtained parental consent for that child to use the Services and disclose Personal Information to us. If you are a student under 13, please do not send any Personal Information to us if your school, district, and/or teacher has not obtained this prior consent from your parent or guardian, and please do not send any Personal Information other than what we request from you in connection with the Services. If we learn we have collected Personal Information from a student under 13 without parental consent from his or her parent or guardian or obtained by his or her school, district, and/or teacher, or if we learn a student under 13 has provided us personal information beyond what we request from him or her, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that a student under 13 may have provided us personal information in violation of this paragraph, please contact us at [info@GrammarFlip.com](mailto:info@GrammarFlip.com).

When we use the term “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are referring to personally identifiable information of individual registrants of the Services.

We will alert you to material changes at least 30 days before they take effect by placing a notice on GrammarFlip.com, by sending you an email, and/or by some other means. We reserve the right, however, to effect important changes more quickly as needed, as in the case of a security threat or other emergency situation. Please note that if you’ve opted not to receive emails from us (or you haven’t provided us with your email address), those legal notices will still govern your use of the Services, and you are still responsible for reading and understanding them. If you use the Services after any changes to the Privacy Policy have been made effective, that means you agree to all of the changes.

We reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any information that we reasonably believe is necessary to comply with law or court order; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of GrammarFlip, our employees, our users, or others.

Your account is protected by a password for your privacy and security. If you access your account via a third party site or service, you may have additional or different sign-on protections via that third party site or service. You must prevent unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password and/or other sign-on mechanism appropriately and limiting access to your computer or device and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account.
